Guide to the John Gunther Papers 1935-1967
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Inside U.S.A.
  - Subseries 9: Informational Correspondence, Memoranda, Etc. (by State)
    - Alabama Arizona Arkansas (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - California (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Colorado Connecticut (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Delaware (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Florida Georgia Idaho (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Illinois (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Indiana (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Iowa (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Kansas Kentucky (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Louisiana (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Maine Maryland (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Massachusetts (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Michigan (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Minnesota (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Mississippi Missouri (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Montana (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Nebraska (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Nevada New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - New York (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - North Carolina North Dakota Ohio (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Oklahoma (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Oregon (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Rhode Island South Carolina South Dakota Tennessee (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Texas (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Utah (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Vermont Virginia (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Washington West Virginia (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Wisconsin (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Wyoming Alaska Hawaii (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (General data on more than one state) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority Missouri Valley Authority (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Henry J. Kaiser and Company (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with lawyers on possible libel (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence requesting permissions to quote (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Personal correspondence (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence in re "The Giant World of Texas," Reader's Digest, July, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence in re "California the Golden," Holiday, January, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 10: Post-Publication Correspondence
    - Correspondence from prominent persons and personal friends of Gunther in response to book (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 11: Correspondence in re Specific States-Post-Publication
    - Alabama Arizona Arkansas (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - California (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Colorado Florida (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Georgia Idaho Illinois (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Indiana Iowa Kansas (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Kentucky Louisiana (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Maine Maryland Massachusetts (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Michigan Minnesota Mississippi (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Missouri Montana (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - New York (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - North Carolina North Dakota Ohio (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Oklahoma Oregon (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Rhode Island South Carolina South Dakota Tennessee (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Texas (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Utah (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Vermont Virginia (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Washington West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority Missouri Valley Authority (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - West Middlewest (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - New England (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - South (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Negroes (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - "Finale" (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 12: General Correspondence
    - A (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - B (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - C-D (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - E-F (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - G (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - H (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - J-K (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - I-N (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - O-R (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - S-T (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - W-Y, unsigned (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 13: Correspondence-1951 Revision
    - Informational correspondence (pre-publication) (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Post-publication correspondence-A-J (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Post-publication correspondence-K-Z (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (post-publication) on Gunther and Inside USA (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 14: Research Notes-Alabama
    - Interview notes, John H. Bankhead (U.S. Senator) Jonathan Daniels (editor, Raleigh (N.C.) News & Observer) Chauncey Sparks (former governor) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Notes on Tuskegee Institute Miscellaneous notes Names; outline (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 15: Research Notes-Arizona
    - Interview notes, Ben Avery (editor) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Interview notes, William Chamberlain (Assistant to Governor) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Interview notes, M. G. Dougherty (Arizona Power Authority) H. S. McClusky (Industrial Commission Referee) Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names; outline (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 16: Research Notes-Arkansas
    - Interview notes, Carl Bailey (former governor) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Interview notes, William Fulbright (U.S. Senator) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Interview notes, Sam Peck (hotel owner) Miscellaneous notes (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 17: Research Notes-California
    - Interview notes, Earl Behrens (San Francisco Chronicle) Manchester Boddy (Editor, Los Angeles News) Royce Brier (San Francisco Chronicle) George Cameron (Publisher, San Francisco Chronicle) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Interview notes, Margaret Chung (San Francisco M.D., civic leader) Bartley Crum (San Francisco businessman) Ernest Cuneo (New York lawyer) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Interview notes, Henry Dickinson (attorney) Sheridan Downey (U.S. Senator) Walter Duranty (writer) Clarence Dykstra (Provost, University of California) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Interview notes, John Elliott (Businessman) (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, Robert Flippin (Social worker) C. J. Haggerty (Labor leader) Alexander Heron (State official) Joseph Jackson (San Francisco Chronicle) (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Interview notes, Robert Kenny (Attorney General) (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Interview notes, Harley Knox (Mayor, San Diego) (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Interview notes, Roger Lapham (Mayor, San Francisco) Henry Mankiewicz (Movie producer) George Pepper (Movie executive) George Roberts (Labor leader) James Roosevelt (U.S. Congressman) (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Interview notes, Chester Rowell (San Francisco Chronicle) (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Interview notes, Paul Smith (editor, San Francisco Chronicle) Jerry Voorhis (former Congressman) Walter Wanger (Movie producer) Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Names; outlines (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 18: Research Notes-Colorado
    - Interview notes, Claude Boettcher (industrialist) D. D. Campbell (businessman) Ben Cherrington (Acting Chancellor, University of Denver) Frank Darvell (British consul, Denver) (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Interview notes, Roscoe Fleming (writer) (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Interview notes, Morris Garnsey (Professor, University of Colorado) Charles A. Graham (MVA attorney) George Hill (labor leader) E. D. Nicholson (United Airlines official) (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Interview notes, Benton Stong (Editor, National Union Farmer) John Vivian (governor) Robert Warren (state official) Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous notes; names (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 19: Research Notes-Connecticut
    - Interview notes, Raymond Baldwin (Governor, U.S. Senator) Francis Murphy (Manager, Hartford Times) Charles Seymour (President, Yale University) M. S. Sherman (Editor, Hartford Courant) Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 20: Research Notes-Delaware
    - Interview notes, Harold Brayman (Publicity Director, DuPont Co.) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Interview notes, Henry T. Claus (Publisher, Wilmington Morning News) H. L. Mencken (writer) Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 21: Research Notes-Florida
    - Interview notes, Daniel Mahoney (Manager, Miami Daily News) Outland W. D. Outman (Florida Legislative Representative in Washington) Claude Pepper (U.S. Senator) Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notes; outline (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 22: Research Notes-Georgia
    - Interview notes, Ellis Arnall (governor) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Interview notes, Margaret Fisher (writer) George Glenn (President, Exposition Cotton Mills) Harrison Jones (Chairman of Board, Coca Cola Co.) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Interview notes, John Paschall (editor, Atlanta Journal) (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Interview notes, Richard Rich Jack Tarver (Atlanta Constitution) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Interview notes, M. E. Thompson (Secretary to governor) Josephine Wilkins (Citizens' Fact-Finding Committee) Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous notes; names, outlines (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 23: Research Notes-Idaho
    - Interview notes, Glenn Taylor (U.S. Senator) University officials Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 24: Research Notes-Illinois
    - Interview notes, Richard Finnegan (Editor, Chicago Times) Robert Hutchins (Chancellor, University of Chicago) Lloyd Lewis (journalist) (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, Raymond McKeough (labor leader) Milton Mayer (writer, University of Chicago) Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Notes on Negroes Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 25: Research Notes-Indiana
    - Interview notes, Charles LaFollette (U.S. Congressman) Walter Leckrone (editor, Indianapolis Times) Miscellaneous Names, outline (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 26: Research Notes-Iowa
    - Interview notes, Robert Blue (governor) Scott Ellis (farmer) (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Interview notes, John Henry (Des Moines Register & Tribune) (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Interview notes, Allan Kline (President) (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Interview notes, Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Notes on trip to an Iowa farm Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 27: Research Notes-Kansas
    - Interview notes, "C & M" Alf Landon (politician) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Interview notes, William Long (state official) Andrew Schoeppel (Governor) Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes, names (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 28: Research Notes-Kentucky
    - Interview notes, Lisle Baker (Louisville Courrier-Journal) James Pope (Louisville Courrier-Journal) (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Interview notes, Wilson Wyatt (Mayor, Louisville) (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names; outline (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 29: Research Notes-Louisiana
    - Interview notes, George Healy (Editor, New Orleans Times-Picayune) Andrew Higgins (industrialist) (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Interview notes, Harnett Kane (writer) Charles Manship (Publisher, Baton Rouge State Times) Robbins Heda Von Meysenburg Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 30: Research Notes-Maine
    - Interview notes, Ralph Flanders (U.S. Senator, Vermont) Horace Hildreth (Governor-elect) Secretary to Gov. Sewall Sumner Sewall (Governor) Interview notes -Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes, names (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 31: Research Notes-Maryland
    - Interview notes, H. L. Mencken (writer) Miscellaneous, Miscellaneous notes (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 32: Research Notes-Massachusetts
    - Interview notes, Erwin Canham (Editor, Christian Science Monitor) Robert Choate (Publisher, Boston Herald) Frederick Church (Insurance executive) Karl Compton (President, Massachusetts Institute of Technology) (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Interview notes, James Conant (President, Harvard University) (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Interview notes, James Curley (former Mayor, Boston) Charles Curtis (writer) Williard DaLue (Boston Globe) Carl Friedrich (Professor, Harvard University) P. Gardener (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Interview notes, Russell Gerould (Secretary to Governor Saltonstall) (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, Mrs. Homans Joseph Martin (U.S. Congressman) W. E. Mullins (Boston Herald) Murdoch (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Interview notes, Levarett Saltonstall (Governor) (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Interview notes, Maurice Tobin (Mayor, Boston) Edward Weeks (Editor, Atlantic Monthly) Laurence Winship (Editor, Boston Globe) Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 33: Research Notes-Michigan
    - Interview notes, Malcolm Hingay (Detroit Free Press) Charles Carll (Ford News Bureau) (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Interview notes, David Connery (labor leader) (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Interview notes, Richard Frankensteen (labor leader) James McClendon (NAACF leader) H. T. McCreedy (labor leader) (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Interview notes, Victor Reuther (labor leader) (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Interview notes, Walter Reuther (labor leader) (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Interview notes, R. J. Thomas (labor leader) Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outline (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 34: Research Notes-Minnesota
    - Interview notes, Joseph Ball (U.S. Senator) Elmer Benson (former governor) Hubert Humphrey (Mayor, Minneapolis) (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Interview notes, John Jacobsen (Labor leader) Walter Judd (U.S. Congressman) "Red" Lewis (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Interview notes, Mark Nolan (District court judge) Roger Rutchick (Secretary to Gov. Benson) (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Interview notes, Gideon Seymour (Editor, Minneapolis Star-Journal) J. Russell Wiggins (Editor, St. Paul Pioneer Press) Robert Wishert (Labor leader) Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Notes on trips to Hibbing and Sauk Center (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous notes; names (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 35: Research Notes-Mississippi
    - Interview notes, Thomas Bailey (governor) Frederick Sullens (Editor, Jackson Daily News) Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 36: Research Notes-Missouri
    - Interview notes, John Cauley (Kansas City Star) Ralph Coughlan (St. Louis Poat-Dispatch) Courtney Crouch (businessman) Chester Davis (banker) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Interview notes, W. A. Halloway (Labor leader) Joseph Fulitzer (St. Louis Post-Dispatch) Benjamin Reese (Editor, St. Louis Post-Dispatch) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Interview notes, Roy Roberts (Editor, Kansas City Star) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Interview notes, Harry S. Truman (Vice President) Raymond Tucker (Washington University professor) Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 37: Research Notes-Montana
    - Interview notes, Fred Bennion (Secretary, Montana Taxpayers' Association Thomas Campbell (farmer) Allen Cowperthwaite (Independent Record) Robert Fletcher (Montana Power Company) (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Interview notes, John Howard (author, journalist) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Interview notes, Howard Johnson (Chief Justice, Montana Supreme Court) (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, H. Lowndes Maury (Attorney) (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Interview notes, James Murray (U.S. Senator) James O'Connell (U.S. Congressman) "O'D." Paul Raver (Bonneville Power Administration) (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Interview notes, Marjorie Sammons (Editor, Copper Commando) Mildred Stoltz (Education Director, Farmer's Union) O.S. Warden (Publisher, Great Falls Tribune) (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Interview notes, William Wells (Porter Bros. Corp.) Burton K. Wheeler (U.S. Senator) Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 38: Research Notes-Nebraska
    - Interview notes, Walter Christenson (Editor, Omaha World Herald) (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Interview notes, Dwight Griswold (governor) (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Interview notes, J. E. Lawrence (Editor, Lincoln Star) (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Interview notes, Stanley Matzke (State official) Robert Simmons (Chief Justice, State Supreme Court) Kenneth Wherry (U.S. Senator) (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Interview notes, Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 39: Research Notes-Nevada
    - Interview notes, Alan Bible (Attorney General) Kenneth Johnson (State Senator) Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Notes on trip to Virginia City (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 40: Research Notes-New Hampshire
    - Interview notes, Robert Blood (Governor) James Langley (Editor, Concord Daily Monitor) Donald Tuttle (Planning and Development Commission) Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 41: Research Notes-New Jersey
    - Interview notes, J. Douglas Brown (Princeton University Professor) Harold Dodds (President, Princeton University) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Interview notes, Walter Edge (governor) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Interview notes, Edward Gilroy (Secretary to Gov. Edge) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Interview notes, James Kerney (Editor, Trenton Times) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 42: Research Notes-New Mexico
    - Interview notes, John Collier (Commissioner of Indian Affairs) John Dempsey (former governor) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Interview notes, John Evans (Superintendent, Pueblos Agency) Carl Hatch (U.S. Senator) Dorothy Larson (writer) Mable Dodge Luhan (writer) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Interview notes, Frank Rand (Santa Fe New Mexican) J. William Strode (Secretary to governor) Clyde Tingley (Mayor, Albuquerque) Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 43: Research Notes-New York
    - Interview notes, Hamilton Fish Armstrong (Editor, Foreign Affairs) Morris Ernst (Attorney, writer) (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Interview notes, Thomas Finletter (Attorney) (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Interview notes, Fiorella LaGuardia (Mayor, New York City) (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Interview notes, Reuben Lazarus (Secretary to Mayor LaGuardia) (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, Paul Lockwood (Secretary to Gov. Dewey) Robert Moses (State and city official) Barnet Nover (Washington Post) (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Interview notes, William O'Dwyer (Mayor, New York City) James Wadsworth (U.S. Congressman) Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Notes on Harlem and Negroes; on "walk around the block" (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 44: Research Notes-North Carolina
    - Interview notes, Josephus Daniels (Publisher, Raleigh News & Observer) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Interview notes, Frank Graham (President, University of North Carolina) (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Interview notes, Robert Madry (University of North Carolina) Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 45: Research Notes-North Dakota
    - Interview notes, C. B. Baldwin (Labor leader) (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Interview notes, Walter Christenson (Editor, Omaha World Herald) Gaylord Conrad (Editor, Bismarck Capital) (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Interview notes, A. L. Hellebust, Martin Byrne (Farmers Union officials) (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Interview notes, Benton Stong (Editor, National Union Farmer) Glenn Talbot (President, Farmers Union) Frank Vogel (Non-Partisan League) Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 46: Research Notes-Ohio
    - Interview notes, Louis Bromfield (author) Harold Burton (U.S. Senator) (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Interview notes, John Ellis (City Solicitor, Cincinnati) (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Interview notes, Brooks Emeny (Cleveland Council on World Affairs) (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Interview notes, Jack Kroll (labor leader) Frank Lausche (governor) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Interview notes, Walter Leckrone (editor, Indianapolis Times) John Lokar (Secretary to Gov. Lausche) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Interview notes, Roderick Peattie (Ohio State University professor) (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Interview notes, Pierson (Cincinnati banker) Clarence Ridley (Director, City Managers Association) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Interview notes, Louis Seltzer (Editor, Cleveland Press) Hulbert Taft (Editor, Cincinnati Times-Star) Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 47: Research Notes-Oklahoma
    - Interview notes, John Collier (Commissioner of Indian Affairs) Robert Kerr (governor) Savoie Lottinville (University of Oklahoma Press) (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Interview notes, A. S. ("Mike") Monroney (U.S. Senator) R. M. Rainey (Judge) Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Interview notes, "C.I.O." officials Redford Bond (Chairman, Public Utilities Commission), Ben Dwight (Principal Chief, Choctaw tribe), May tubby (Governor, Chickasaw tribe), Earl Welch (Justice, State Supreme Court) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outline (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 48: Research Notes-Oregon
    - Interview notes, Roy Atkinson (Washington State labor leader) Howard Cosign (Washington State radio commentator) R. A. Fenton (M.D.) (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Interview notes, Nelson Heseltine (Bonneville Power Administration) (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Interview notes, Nannie Wood Honeyman (Collector of Customs, Portland) E. Palmer Hoyt (Publisher, The Oregonian) Ronald Jones (Farmers' Union) (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Interview notes, Wayne Morse (U.S. Senator) (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Interview notes, Jerry O'Connell (Democratic Party official, Washington State) Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outline (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 49: Research Notes-Pennsylvania
    - Interview notes, I.Z. Buckwalter (Lancaster Newspapers, Inc.) Mrs. B. Buller (Lancaster Newspapers, Inc.) Orville Bullitt (Philadelphia civic leader) Jerry Conn (Lancaster journalist) Joseph Donoghue (Labor leader) (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Interview notes, George Earle (governor) Thomas D. Finletter (judge) Ben Fischer (Labor leader) Joseph Guffey (U.S. Senator) Gilbert Kraus (Philadelphia attorney) (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Interview notes, David Lawrence (Mayor, Pittsburgh) Ross Leffler (Steel company executive) Robert McLean (President, Philadelphia Bulletin) Edward Martin (governor) (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Interview notes, George Pepper (U.S. Senator) John Rich (American Friends Service Committee) (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Interview notes, Harold Ruttenberg (Research Director, United Steel Workers) (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Interview notes, Harry Saylor (Editor, Philadelphia Record) Edgar Scott (Stockbroker) (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Interview notes, J. David Stern (Publisher, Philadelphia Record) John Wisniewski (steelworker) Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Notes on Independence Hall; iron and steel industry (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Notes on the Negro press (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous notes Names, outlines (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 50: Research Notes-Rhode Island
    - Interview notes, Sevellon Brown (Publisher, Providence Journal) Frederick Kilguss (Secretary to Gov. McGrath) J. Howard McGrath (governor) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 51: Research Notes-South Carolina
    - Interview notes, W. W. Ball (Editor, Charleston News & Courier) Josephine Pinckney (author) Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 52: Research Notes-South Dakota
    - Interview notes, Fred Christopherson (Editor, Sioux Falls Argus-Leader Eugene Mahoney (Democratic Party official) Miscellaneous Miscellaneous notes Names (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 53: Research Notes-Tennessee
    - Interview notes, E. H. Crump (Political boss) (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Interview notes, Silliman Evans (Publisher, Nashville Tennessean) (Box 40, Folder 10)